STACK

- React JS
- Tailwind CSS
- Javascript
- HTML5
- CSS3
- Redux JS
- Node JS
- PosgreSQL
- Express
- Scrum

I am a programmer with strong soft skills, excelling in communication, teamwork, adaptability to changes, leadership, self-learning, and more. I have a solid experience in HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Tailwind, and ReactJS, specializing in front-end web development and creating high performance interactive interfaces

CONTACT



<u>Portfolio</u>



+57 3212159041



edwar.leon.m@gmail.com



<u>LinkedIn</u>

SOFT SKILLS

Leadership

Communication

Adaptability to changes

Self-learning

Teamwork

LANGUAGES

English B1

Native Spanish

LEÓN EDWAR

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

EDUCATION

MAY 2023 - PRESENT

Full Stack Web Developer - Academio

Outstanding student in the fundamentals and React JS modules, creating projects with solid foundations in full stacks. Link <u>here</u>.

APRIL 2022 - SEPTEMBER 2022

WEB DEVELOPER - Alura (ONE)

Link here.

EXPERIENCE

NOVEMBER 2023 - CURRENT

Kaba Clubs

TECHNICAL LEAD- FRONTEND DEV

Leading a multifunctional team to craft innovative solutions. Implementing agile methodologies, streamlining processes, and steering successful projects, showcasing superior technical and managerial skills. Programming and designing the views of the vendor portal.

AUGUST 2023 - JANUARY 2024 Linde

LOGISTICS COORDINATOR

Ensuring national transportation of vehicles carrying vital gases such as Argon, Oxygen, CO2, and Nitrogen for food companies and hospitals. Supervising drivers' schedules and satellite tracking of vehicles, ensuring precise deliveries.

PROJECTS

E-COMMERCE - PORTAL USUARIOS

- Purchase and service procurement registration and control application for Kaba Clubs e-commerce, managing refunds, purchasing processes, and more.
- For this project, we utilized React.js, Tailwind CSS, Redux.js, Git, API consumption, and Laravel.

POKEDEX

- Web application for searching Pokémon and accessing their abilities and statistics.
- This project utilized React Js, Tailwind, Redux Js, Git, and API consumption.
- · Repository link, Project link

RICK AND MORTY APP

- Web application for searching characters from the series and learning about their origin and status.
- This project employed React Js, Tailwind, Redux Js, Git, and API consumption.
- Repository link, Project link